BLACK SABBATH
" Freely adapted from stories ...
by Chekhov , Tolstoy , and Maupassant "
Come closer , please .
I have something to tell you .
Ladies and gentlemen , I am Boris Karloff .
Allow me to introduce ...
three brief tales of terror and the supernatural .
I hope you didn 't come to the movies alone .
As you will realize by watching this film ...
specters and vampires ...
are everywhere .
There might be one sitting next to you .
Yes , they go to the movies , too , I assure you .
Vampires look perfectly normal , which , in fact , they are .
Except ...
they have a strange habit of drinking blood .
Especially the blood of those they love .
But here I am chattering on and wasting time .
So let 's get on with our first tale .
THE TELEPHONE
Hello . Hello ?
Hello .
You 're so beautiful . Too beautiful , Rosy .
Who is this ?
You 'll know right before you die .
I can see your heavenly body .
Your silky arms ...
your perfect legs .
No , don 't cover them up .
A body like yours can drive a man to madness .
And I will kill you .
Who is this ? Who are you ?
Hello .
Why did you put your robe on ?
You should have stayed as you were .
I like you better with nothing on .
That 's how I want to find you .
I 'll get in , even if you lock the door .
Who are you ?
- What do you want from me ? - I told you .
I want to kill you . I want revenge .
You did well to turn on all the lights .
I want to see you die . Do you understand , Rosy ?
I know you 're listening .
I saw you , you know ? You hid your money and jewels .
How stupid .
You haven 't changed . You don 't get it , do you ?
I 'm not interested in money- - I want you !
I want your splendid body . And I 'll have you . I will !
NOt to caress you , but to wring your neck .
To choke you until you suffocate .
And I 'll do it , Rosy . You 'll see !
Who is this ?
Who are you ? Answer me !
I beg of you . I can 't take it anymore . Why do you hate me ?
What have I done to you ?
Don 't drive me mad like this . Answer me , please !
" Frank Rainer Has Escaped ... "
You 're beginning to understand , huh , Rosy ?
Tell me the truth . : You weren 't expecting it , were you ?
But I escaped just to come and find you .
And finally I 'm close to you . Very close , Rosy .
And you can 't do anything about it .
Calling the police is useless .
Because I 'm closer than the police .
Don 't you forget it . : much closer .
Frank , listen .
Listen to me , Frank !
- Hello . - Mary , it 's Rosy .
Hi , honey !
I really didn 't expect your call .
You said you didn 't want to see or speak to me anymore .
Please , now 's not the time .
- Frank has escaped . - Yes , I read about it .
So why are you telling me ? Now you two will get back together .
Mary , cut it out . I 'm scared .
He wants revenge , I 'm sure of it .
Come over right away , please !
You want me to come to you ?
Did I hear correctly ?
Yes , yes . I beg you . As fast as you can .
He wants to kill me .
All right , honey . I don 't bear grudges .
Give me five minutes .
Thank you . Hurry .
Why did you go and call your friend Mary ?
Are you hoping she can help you ?
Did you think I wouldn 't hear ?
You spoke in a whisper , but it 's no use .
Because I 'm close , I told you .
Very close .
Call whoever you want , Rosy .
It 's all of no use .
Even if you had an army around you .
By dawn , you will be dead .
Do you hear me , Rosy ?
By dawn ...
you will be dead !
Rosy , it 's me . Let me in .
- Hi . In trouble ? - How did you get in ?
The door was open .
Look at all this light .
What , are you the mistress of the guy who reads the meter ?
Sorry .
I was forgetting that you have a fine palate .
It must be the CEO of the company .
I see you haven 't changed anything here .
Everything 's just as it was when we were friends ...
and I came over all the time .
Just like old times .
Come on , honey . Tell Mary everything .
Please , I 'm not in the mood for humor . Believe me .
All right , Rosy .
As you wish . No jokes .
He 's been calling me since I got home .
He 's been saying terrible things , with a cold , threatening voice .
He knows everything I do , sees my every move .
The first time he called , I was in my bathrobe ...
and he knew it .
Then I put my house robe on ...
and he knew that too .
He even knew right away that I had called you .
It 's as if he were in the room ...
spying on me , ready to kill me .
Don 't be silly .
He 's guessing . He 's going on a hunch .
I thought so too ...
but how did he know I called you ?
He called me right after that .
He always knew about us .
But what he doesn 't know ...
is that you swore never to see me again .
He told me I 'll die before dawn .
He 's an exploiter , not a killer .
Trust me , he was just trying to frighten you .
Mary , I 'm the one who turned him in ...
and he knows it .
I 'm scared .
Come , come .
I 'm here now .
Tomorrow we 'll go to the police together .
He can call all he wants now .
Come on , give me a nightgown .
In the meantime , I 'll make you some tea .
What are you doing with that knife ?
You never know .
- Still afraid ? - No , I 'm better now .
Come on , then . Go to bed .
What 's that ?
Poison .
Compliments of Frank .
It 's a tranquilizer , silly .
It will do you good .
Can 't you see how shaken up you are ?
" Dear rosy , I 'm sorry I frightened you so ...
but it was the only way for me to get you to reconsider ...
your decision that caused me such pain .
Reading about Frank 's escape gave me the idea .
The voice you heard ... was mine .
Don 't hate me for it .
Was seeing me again really so bad ? "
Damn you !
Always where you shouldn 't be .
THE WURDULAK
Who gave you that dagger ?
Is this how you welcome strangers in this house ?
With a gun ?
- Who are you ? - I am Count Vladimir d 'Urfé .
I wasn 't planning on stopping here . I was headed for Gersy .
Forgive me , sir ...
but this knife belongs to my father .
Take it .
Where did you find it ?
Come and see .
He was on the horse . He 's gone .
I ran my sword through his heart .
Now he can 't hurt anyone anymore .
If you killed him , may God bless you .
Is it Alibeq ?
He was the only one in the area ...
who dressed like this .
- Haven 't you heard of Alibeq ? - No .
A Turkish criminal , sir . A horrible man .
He killed many people around here .
You saw me , I ran through his heart . You should have done it .
I should have done it ? Why on earth ?
They say he was a wurdulak .
When he found him , this was in his back .
We lived in fear .
No one was safe ...
and the number of victims grew day by day .
Any other scourge would have been easier to bear .
When Alibeq killed our foreman ...
my father decided it was time to hunt down that cursed Turk ...
and stop him once and for all .
My brother and I wanted to go with him ...
but he wouldn 't let us .
My father and master will not be contradicted .
Thank you .
- What 's your name ? - Sdenka .
A strange but beautiful name . I 've never heard it before .
Well , the Turk you were so afraid of is dead .
I drink to the health of whoever killed him .
Yes , Alibeq is dead .
Now the only one we have to fear is our father .
I don 't understand . You should be happy .
The nightmare is over , but you 're still afraid !
If our father does not return within two hours ...
you must be on your way , for your own good .
To stay here , even for one night ...
could prove fatal , believe me .
Why did you not heed my brother 's advice ?
I could say that I 'm too tired to continue my journey ...
or that the conversation piqued my curiosity .
But that wouldn 't be the truth .
You 're the reason I stayed .
You 're very kind , sir ...
but if my father should return after midnight ...
there is little you could do for me ...
and you yourself would be in danger .
You must leave .
Calm yourself , Sdenka . I 'm sure there 's no cause for such alarm .
I 'm sure your father isn 't a monster .
Don 't make jokes about this !
- I didn 't mean to offend you . - I know . You don 't understand .
Tell me what this is all about .
Please . I may be able to help you . Trust me , Sdenka .
Before my father left , he said ...
" I 'll be back within five days .
But if I should come back after five days have passed ...
do not let me in ...
but drive a dagger through my heart ...
because it will mean I too have become a wurdulak . "
Your brother used this word too , but I don 't know what it means .
If you had been born in these parts ...
you would be afraid even to say the word .
I 'll tell you what it means .
The wurdulak are bloodthirsty corpses .
They yearn for the blood of those they loved most when they were alive .
Sdenka , you can 't really believe that old legend .
You say that , but the legend is true .
The more they 've loved someone , the more they long to kill them ...
to suck their blood .
Those killed in this way also become wurdulak ...
until someone manages to stab them in the heart .
And when are the five days up ?
Tonight , at the stroke of midnight .
Thank heavens . It 's him !
Yes , it 's him .
But how are we to know ...
whether the five days have passed or not ?
- The clock just struck midnight . - God help us .
Well ? Why does no one ...
come to embrace me ?
I 'm wounded .
Why do you stare at me and say nothing ?
What is the meaning of this silence ?
Five days on the mountain ...
have changed me so ...
that even my dog doesn 't recognize me .
You hear that ? He admits five days have gone by !
Let me wrap your wound .
Go away !
You 'll hurt me .
Your wound- - it 's in the heart .
I 'm hungry now .
Do you intend to stay long ?
Just for the night . I 'm going to Gersy .
Tell everyone you meet ...
that old Gorca killed Alibeq .
Of course , if you 'd like .
It was a great deed . Tell us how it went .
He 's dead . There 's nothing to tell .
The game is over .
- What 's that ? - Lamb .
No meat !
I 'm not hungry anymore .
My bones are frozen from the cold , and my throat feels tight .
Somebody go and make that cursed dog shut up !
I told you to shut him up .
Do you no longer follow my orders ?
- But it 's your favorite dog , Father . - Kill it !
Kill it !
Ivan .
What 's wrong with you , woman ?
Are you trying to prevent me from holding my grandson ?
Give him to me !
Come , Ivan . Give Grandpa a big kiss .
Father , it 's late .
The child is sleepy .
Go on to bed , Ivan . Good night .
Do you know , sir , that I found Alibeq 's corpse ?
How do you know it was really him ?
There 's no doubt about it .
His clothing , his jewels . And your dagger .
My dagger ?
Do you think that 's enough to identify a headless corpse ?
No one would be willing to accept this as proof ...
and people would quake with fear , as they did before .
But I ...
and I alone have proof that Alibeq is dead .
That 's why the dog was howling .
He smelled a corpse .
Take it .
Hang it in front of the house for all to see .
Don 't worry , go to sleep .
You too , Sdenka . Go to bed . I 'll keep watch .
I don 't think it 's necessary . He 's just wounded .
He 's not just wounded . You saw that he wouldn 't eat .
Have Pietro take the watch . You 've been awake too many nights .
Maria is right . I 'll stay up .
You sleep upstairs with them .
Where are you taking me , Grandpa ?
I have a surprise for you right outside . It 's a secret .
Giorgio , Gorca took the child . Hurry !
Pietro !
Come back !
Give me back my son !
Ivan !
I can 't believe it .
Pietro is dead ...
and perhaps by now the child is too .
It 's like a nightmare .
A terrible nightmare I want to wake up from ...
but I can 't , I can 't !
My God !
Sdenka , listen to me .
As long as you stay in this house , the nightmare will never end .
Please , listen . Run away with me .
No , I can 't .
Don 't you understand it 's madness to stay here ?
There are days of terror in store for you here .
You can 't throw your life away . Come away with me , Sdenka !
No , my destiny is here .
That 's not true .
Your destiny is to be happy and free ...
and loved , above all .
Love , happiness .
You speak of things I can never have again .
But they can be yours .
You can stay with me forever , if you wish .
- It 's impossible . - I love you .
And perhaps one day , when this nightmare is over ...
you will love me too .
Ivan !
Come now , Maria .
I beg you , don 't do it . Stab me instead .
It 's for the peace of his soul .
I did the same to Pietro .
Not him ! Not him !
I 'm warning you , Giorgio .
If you do it , I 'll kill myself !
I won 't let you do it , do you hear ?
Mama .
I 'm cold .
- Is it Ivan ? - No , it 's the wind .
- I 'm cold . - For God 's sake , Maria , don 't listen !
But it 's my little boy calling me . He 's cold !
He 's dead- - dead !
Be reasonable . You buried him yourself !
Let go of me ! I have to let him in . He 's cold .
It 's not your son . It 's a wurdulak !
I don 't care . Let me go or I 'll kill you !
Let me in .
I 'm cold .
Don 't go .
Come back !
Come , don 't be afraid . We 'll be safe in this old convent .
- We should have kept going . - We 're far away . The horse is tired .
Wait here .
We can sleep here .
It may not be very cozy , but as soon as it 's light out ...
we 'll go on to Gersy .
What is it ?
Nothing .
Sdenka , listen .
Yes , we 've run away , but you must try to forget .
If you don 't forget , you 'll be running forever .
Vladimir , I beg you ...
try to understand .
How many times do I have to tell you that I love you ...
and that if you don 't find the strength to act ...
you will destroy your life and mine ?
No , I beg you .
Darling , forgive me .
Don 't cry .
Father !
Where are you ?
You shouldn 't have run away . Why did you do it ?
Father , have mercy on me .
Let me live . This man loves me .
Sdenka , no one can love you more than we do .
My love , I thought- -
I didn 't expect you .
Why did you leave me ? Why did you come back here ?
I did it out of love for you .
They had come to kill you .
Go .
Go now while there 's still time .
I must stay here now .
You know I 'd rather die than lose you .
Now I know you love me , Vladimir .
I know you love me more than life itself .
My lips are dead without your kisses .
Don 't wait any longer .
Kiss me .
My love .
THE DROP OF WATER
Hello .
Hello ? Yes .
Yes , it 's me . Good evening .
You want me to come at this hour ?
Yes , of course , but- -
Couldn 't we make it tomorrow morning ? I could come very early .
Come on , please . Don 't be like that .
I don 't see the necessity for it .
Yes , all right .
I understand . Stop it , I said I 'm coming .
I told you I 'm coming . Give me time to get there !
What an idiot !
Stupid idiot !
- Who is it ? - It 's me . Open up .
Miss Chester , what took you so long ?
Don 't be ridiculous . I rushed over .
I ran the whole way .
I 'm so frightened .
Believe me , I tried to do it myself , but I couldn 't .
Only you can help me . You 're a trained nurse .
What a great idea ...
with this cursed weather !
- I bet you won 't even pay me . - Don 't worry about that .
There are still a few shillings in the house . I 'll pay you .
- Couldn 't you call a relative ? - You know she didn 't have any .
She had no friends , other than the ones who made the table shake .
There she is .
Are you going to stay there ? Aren 't you going to help me ?
No , miss . Please . I can 't help myself .
Don 't ask me to help .
I didn 't touch her .
She 's just as the doctor left her .
I can see that .
Did you at least get the dress ready ?
Yes , of course . I ironed it , too .
Come with me .
Poor countess . She died all alone .
She deserved better , believe me .
Just look at this lamp .
Good thing it didn 't burn the dress .
- No one will come to the funeral . - Why not ?
- Because they 're afraid , that 's why . - Afraid of what ?
They say that the spirits of the dead killed her . Ghosts !
- What nonsense . - Not really , Miss Chester .
It 's easy for you to say .
But if you knew how she died- -
What do you mean ? She died of a heart attack .
I should know . I kept her going with camphor shots .
It 's what the doctor said , too , right ?
I know , I know .
But that doesn 't mean anything .
The truth is that she died during one of those séances .
While she was in a trance , you see . She was in a trance !
She 'd become obsessed with talking to the dead . Poor woman .
Every Friday she held a séance , come rain or shine .
With a weak heart like hers .
Talking to the dead . There 's a good cure .
Well , let 's get this over with .
I need a pair of stockings too .
Right away .
Are you going to spend the night ?
No , God forbid . I 'm leaving with you .
Hurry up . I need shoes too .
It won 't be easy to find them . She never went out .
- Did you find them ? - Not yet .
There must be at least one pair .
What happened ?
Nothing .
Nothing , don 't worry .
I finally found them .
Stay there . Give them here .
Oh , my God ! What 's happening ?
Nothing .
Let 's go .
We 're done .
Who 's there ?
Have mercy ! Mercy !
So as soon as you heard screaming ...
you ran upstairs and broke down the door .
Yes . But I wasn 't alone , you know .
The neighbors came running too .
We tried pushing on the door , but it was locked .
We kept at it and finally managed to open it .
I saw her dead on the floor , so I made everyone leave .
Nothing has been touched .
I know what to do in cases like this .
I called the police right away .
She had already prepared her nightgown .
Evidently she was about to go to bed .
Death by self-suffocation .
It looks like someone wrenched a ring from her finger .
So there it is .
Didn 't you see that end coming ?
There 's no fooling around with ghosts , because they take revenge .
Well , we 've come to the end of our tales ...
so , sadly , I must leave you now .
But watch out on the way home .
Look around you , look behind you .
Careful when you open the door .
And don 't go in without turning on the light !
Dream about me !
We 'll become friends !
Subs ripped by Ingolf 2004